According to YouTube statistics, only a
small percentage of people that watch my
videos are actually subscribed. So, if
you end up liking this video, consider
subscribing. It's free and you can
always unsubscribe. He's gay.
I'm 100% sure he's gay.
>> [music]
>> So, then we started this conversation.
Headquarters and I.
How can we use that to our benefit? Did
he have a wife? No.
He's single.
>> Which was unusual at his age. How did
you know he was gay?
>> [music]
>> Oh, I
I just It was a vibe.
Okay.
So,
headquarters says,
"We want you to pretend that you're
gay."
I said, "Oh, come on, you guys."
"No, [music] we really need the
information. You got to pretend that
you're gay."
I said, "Okay. I'll do it.
>> [music]
>> I'll do it for Uncle Sam." Are hit men
real? Yes.
At the National Security Council, there
is a committee [music] that meets every
Tuesday morning at 9:00 to draw up
something called the kill list.
>> [music]
>> They sit around a table and they make a
list of all the people that they want to
kill that week. And then they take it
back to the CIA, which has a dedicated
[music]
unit. I won't tell you the name, but it
has a dedicated unit that takes receipt
of the list. They say, "Okay.
Number one, [music] they drive to the
airport, they get on the plane, they go
out to that country. They kill the
person. They come back and then they go
to number two on the list. That happens
[music] every single week. Now, we can
have a conversation about whether that's
right or whether [music] it's wrong.
It's certainly immoral.
It's illegal. But it's been tasked by
the president. Uh at the [music] same
time, they will tell you,
"There hasn't been another 9/11, has
there?"
>> [music]
>> Maybe it's cuz we're out there killing
people. What kind of people would be on
that list? Oh, the the most dangerous
terrorists in the world.
Or at least [music] people that the CIA
deems to be the most dangerous
terrorists.
Can you say what he did to trigger the
meeting? I asked him if he had access to
a target.
>> [music]
>> And he said,
"Not today.
But I could [__] her [music] if I wanted
to."
I said, "Get out of here."
He goes, "She's been flirting with me
for 40 years.
I said well she has something that I
want. [music] Can you get close enough
to her to get it?
And he said yeah. I said then get it. So
he triggered the meeting to say He
[music] [__] her
and she gave him everything that I had
asked for and he [music] wanted to give
it to me.
I said you're a dog, you know that?
You're like an animal. I said you're an
old man, you're you're older than my
father I told [music] him and you're
>> banging women to get information from
them? He's like
This is the life [music] we've chosen
for ourselves.
We said okay, all right.
>> [music]
>> No need to get dramatic.
I [__] love this guy.
I love him. I googled him a few years
ago and and he died. He died about 10
years ago. I was sorry to see him. He
was a genuinely good guy.
>> [music]
>> What's the coolest piece of spy tech you
ever got to use? You know there's kind
of a dirty little secret about spy
[music] tech and it is that 95% of it is
purchased from amazon.com.
Seriously, [music] because it is cheaper
and it is quicker just to go online and
buy it and then use it operationally
than it is to invent it from scratch. Do
you think Jeffrey Epstein was a spy? I
believe very strongly he was a spy, yes.
And who do you think he was working for?
>> I'm confident it was the [music]
Israelis.
>> Why?
Jeffrey Epstein
is kind of the stereotypical example
that they give you in training for
what's called an access [music] agent.
This is a different kind of recruit.
So for example, if you're a foreign
intelligence service and you want
information, like close in information
from a former president
from the CEO of the biggest company in
the world [music]
from a member of the British royal
family. You're not going to recruit
these guys. You're not going to recruit
Bill Clinton or Bill Gates or Prince
Andrew.
So you do the next best thing.
You recruit somebody who has regular
access to them. And that person that you
recruit is going to need to make these
people feel comfortable and appreciated.
And so you give them plenty of money
so he has this house on an island where
he has the whole island and maybe you
bring in young girls, you get them in
compromising positions just in case you
need to use what's called compromat.
Compromising
pictures.
We know We know now that Jeffrey
Epstein's house
on the island
had video cameras
hidden video cameras in literally every
room including the bathrooms.
Why?
Uh why would he care?
What was going on unless it was to use
that information against people?
I'd ask them how the heck do you do
this? Oh,
>> [music]
>> yeah, and they were like, "Well,
there are a lot of threats that take
place at the same time. Yeah, like we
can beat you on the soles of your feet
[music] with a baseball bat
or you can
give us copies of your ledger every day
at the end of [music] the work day.
The Middle East. Your choice. Your
choice. That's right.
The US
How long is it really easy enough to
infiltrate?
Um [music] any FBI agent can go to this
Arab bakery and and they probably
already have gone to the Arab bakery in
the face of Maryland and said, [music]
"Look, you know, we're going to [__] you
up or you're going to give us access
[music] to your books."
It's The US government is far more
worried about uh cryptocurrency. [music]
Mhm. Yeah, that's why you know, I did my
taxes this most recent uh iteration.
They asked me They can ask me three
different [music] times if I had bought
or sold crypto. And then he starts
crying and he says, "Please, brother,
kill me.
Take the [music] pillow and kill me."
And I said, "No, nobody's going to kill
you."
I said, "You're going to get the best
medical care that the American
government can provide.
This is a torture [music] program. They
can use whatever euphemism they want,
but this is a torture program, and
torture's a slippery slope." He said,
"You know how these guys are. Somebody's
going to be a cowboy, they're going to
go overboard, and they're going to kill
the prisoner. And when that happens,
there's going to be a congressional
investigation, then there's going to be
a Justice Department investigation, and
somebody's going to go to prison." "Do
you want to go to prison?" I said, "No,
I don't want to go to prison."
As it turned out, I was the only person
who went to prison. "I [music] said,
your life is over."
So,
now
I'm going to ask you a question [music]
that's going to determine how the rest
of your life is going to be spent.
We know who you are. We know who you
work for, and we know that you're in
charge of the arms cache.
So, I want to know, where are the
weapons? He's like, "Fuck you. I will
never tell you, motherfucker."
So, I That's the wrong answer.
So, he calls me one night, and it was
late. He's a bomb. He's broke. He's just
a terrorist. You can't make any money
from terrorism.
So, um
So, I started paying him. And I was
paying him pretty handsomely, too. And
he was giving me good information, like
operational information. And he wasn't
This terrorist group had sort of fallen
out of fashion, and he became involved
with a group of anarchists. And what
they wanted to do was just
blow [__] up for no reason other than
to, you know, shout, "Yay, anarchy."
Right? So, he calls me one night, and it
was late. It was like 11:00, and he did
the uh
what we call the protocols.
So, like he's like, I said, "Hello." And
I I it was him, cuz I had this phone
that was just for him. It was a burner.
And I said, "Hello." He says, uh
"Hi.
The the rain in Spain falls mainly in
the plain."
And so I said, "Oh, ears eat oats and
dosey doats and little lambs eat ivy."
And he laughed and I laughed and we hung
up.
And that meant meet me in the parking
lot of, you know, the the jumbo toy
store at 2:00 a.m.
So I go down there
and he's like, "I'm I'm desperate. I'm
broke." He goes, "My my daughter's sick.
We have these unexpected medical bills."
And he has this paper bag and it's just
full of gold jewelry. And I said,
"What's this?" He said, "It's all my
wife's jewelry." He said, "Can you buy
it from me?"
And I go, "Dude, I'm not a jeweler."
I I don't know what I I I have no idea
what this stuff is worth. He said, "I'm
desperate." I said, "All right, let's
meet tomorrow
at midnight behind the church in this
northern suburb."
And so I go into work the next day and I
said,
you know, the
the
grasshopper called me in the middle of
the night and tried to sell me his
wife's jewelry.
He goes the station chief says, "Well,
how much does he want?" I said, "He
needs five grand."
He goes, "He's been good. Just give him
the five grand. We'll call it a We'll
call it an early Christmas bonus."
So I met him behind the church. I gave
him five grand.
He's like, "Oh my god, thank you so
much. Thank you. Thank you." He signs
the receipt.
And he was forever indebted to me. He
actually cried when I when I left to
return to headquarters.
He's like, "I'm not sure I can work with
anybody else." I said, "Oh, you're going
to be fine. Everybody else has money
that's just as green as the money that I
carry. You're going to be fine."
What's up, guys? Have you ever killed
anybody? No, thank god. [music] My
children asked me that. And I told them
very proudly that I have never taken any
action that resulted in [music] the
death of another human being.
There's one kind of half exception.
Yeah, yeah, sure. I mean, just a little
half exception. All right, just just
tell me the game. Nothing that would
really count. This will be fine, I'm
sure. So, I went to my desk and I said,
"Good morning, General Powell. This is
John Kiriakou." I [music] gave him my
address. He said, "Thank you."
Hangs up the phone. 8 hours later, we
fired [music] 47 cruise missiles into
Iraqi intelligence headquarters. Don't
go around assuming that our devices are
secure. They're not secure at all.
At all. It's not just, you know, NSA,
CIA, FBI you have to worry about. It's
the British, the French, the Germans,
the Canadians, the Australians, New
Zealanders,
the Russians, the Chinese, the Israelis,
the Iranians.
I mean, everybody has these
capabilities. Capabilities to do what?
To intercept communications. They can
take control of your smart TV remotely,
and they can make the speaker turn into
a a microphone. So, even though the TV
is off,
it can still hear everything that's
being said in the room and broadcast
back to the speaker.
Can make you download genius devices.
Oh, they they could do that when I first
got hired, they were able to do that.
They can take control, again remotely,
of a car's computer system
in order to
well, I mean, in order to to kill you.
Crash the car. Crash the car, take it
off the bridge, take it into a tree.
Well, there's a guy waiting patiently.
He had a bomb stuffed up his ass.
I'm getting married. I'm a member of
this family. I'm a member of this tribe.
I'm getting married. I don't have any
money.
Will you please buy
my living room furniture?
And he'll say, "Yes, of course.
Uh Muhammad,
talk to this guy and get him living room
furniture." The next guy comes up. "Oh,
your highness, thank you for seeing me.
My car broke down and I'm a taxi driver
and I need a new car." "Uh Abdullah,
give this guy a new car." That's a
modulus in Saudi [music] Arabia. Well,
there's a guy waiting patiently in line.
Unbeknownst to to Muhammad bin Nayef or
anybody else, he had a bomb stuffed up
his ass.
Literally, he stuffed the whole bomb up
And when he gets to the front of the
line,
he detonates it. Oh my god. He blows
himself to a thousand pieces, but he
almost kills Muhammad bin Nayef.
Oh, he shoved it up his ass and didn't
even get to kill the guy?
Is there anything that we haven't talked
about that you think is important?
>> [music]
>> 99% of people say no. Some people say,
"What do you mean?"
He said, "Well," [music]
to this janitor, "things like murder,
rape, robbery." Bestiality.
And the guy says, "What was that last
one?"
And my friend says, [music] "I knew I
had him."
He goes, "Bestiality." The guy says,
"What's that mean?"
>> [music]
>> And my friend says,
"It's actually very common." He says,
>> [music]
>> "Everybody does it. It's having sex with
an animal."
And the guy says,
"I may have done that a couple three
times."
>> [music]
>> Jesus Christ. And my friend says, "Okay,
well, like I said, everybody does it,
but just so we can get past it for the
purpose of the polygraph, um in what
cases would you have sex with an
animal?"
The guy says,
"Well, sometimes when I have a fight
with my wife, to get back at her, I go
to the barn and I bugger the horse."
[music]
Cuz it's her horse. He said he gets up
on a step stool and he gets the horse.
>> [music]
>> And he's like,
"Okay, and you've done this more than
once?" He said, "I may have done it a
couple three times."
>> [music]
>> So, he said, needless to say, they
escorted him out of headquarters and
took his badge and said, "Don't ever
come back."
>> [music]